# **Ehab Reda Mohamed**

## Back End Django Developer

I am Back-End web developer (Django) ,with 1 year of experience in web development, and I am seeking for position with an outstanding career opportunity that will offer a rewarding work environment along with a winning team that will fully utilize management skills.

Moba.reda98@gmail.com

+201127907185

Mansoura

in linkedin.com/in/ehab-reda-525696169

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of computer scinece

cairo higher inistitute

10/2016 - 08/2020

GPA 2.87

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Django Developer

Freelancer

05/2018 - Present

## **Java Spring Developer**

Freelancer

08/2016 - 02/2018

## **TECHNOLOGIES**

**DJANGO** 

Python

React

HTML/HTML5

CSS/CSS3

Bootstrap4

## **SKILLS**

Leadership Research Teamwork

Problem solving Time Management

Ability to work under pressure

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

## Pharmacy system

- Add,delete and update company,medicine,order for company and customer.
- Search about any medicine in the list of medicines
- Produce reports to the manager of the pharmacy and the pieces of each bill sold, Admin Dashboard
- MY Tech: DJANGO ,HTML,CSS,Bootstrap4

## Online Shoes Shop System

- Add, delete and update company, Shoes ,order for company and customer
- Search about any Shoe in the list of Shoes
- Produce reports to the manager of the Shop and the pieces of each Shoes sold, Send Mails to Companies, Customers
- MY Tech: DJANGO ,HTML,CSS,Bootstrap4

#### **Blog System**

- Add, delete and update Posts.
- Search for any Blogger, Make a comment on a post.
- Register , Login and Update Profile.
- MY Tech: DJANGO ,HTML,CSS,Bootstrap4.

## **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Professional Working Proficiency

## **INTERESTS**

Database Programming

Reading

Internet

Problem solving